本集字幕将从正片开始
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组&@Daria拽妹黛薇儿
——·@严肃活泼小kk译制·——
嘿 你搞坏我的蛋糕啦
Hey! You're ruining my birthday cake!
她搞砸的才不仅限于此
If only that were all she ruined.
快让她住手
Make her stop!
Daria 她只是个小宝宝
Oh, Daria, she's just a baby.
她也想玩嘛
She wants to play, too!
我真是个萌宝贝
I'm such a cute baby.
为毛我就不能是独生女?
Why can't I be an only child?
就是说嘛 为毛?
Yeah. Why can't I?
坐在这亲眼见证自己的人生走向很美妙吧?
Isn't it great to sit here and see your whole life unfold before your eyes?
就和溺水一样妙不可言
It's almost as good as drowning.
孩子们 猜猜怎么着?
Girls, guess what?
我找到了一盒子我老爹给我童年拍的老家庭电影
I found a box of old home movies my dad took of me when I was a kid!
我把它们转成录像带了
I'm having them transferred to video tape!
我在想我为嘛就从来没有过尴尬阶段呢?
I wonder why I never went through an awkward phase?
他想让你看她出生?
He wanted you to watch her birth?
那能让你产生终生不可磨灭的创伤
That could scar you for life.
我出生就自带创伤
The birth itself did that.
说到永久性的伤害...
Speaking of permanent damage...
我可看不到任何蔬菜哟
I don't see any vegetables!
你应该从我这角度看看
You should have my view.
要蔬菜干嘛?
Why vegetables?
在食物大战中用来扔屏幕么?
To throw at the screen during the big food fight?
什么食物大战?
What food fight?
Daria 你是笨蛋不是?
Daria, are you thick or something?
这是电影节的食物
This is the Food in Film Festival.
你上个月没去看《洛基恐怖秀》吗?
Didn't you see the Rocky Horror Picture Show last month?
Kevin和我穿上了彼此的内衣裤
Kevin and I wore each other's underwear.
又穿了?
Again?
真抱歉让你失望了
Sorry to disappoint you,
可我不觉得这很有意思
but I don't think this is an interactive event.
今晚他们要播《Andre Sakarynsky的最后晚餐》
Tonight they're showing Andre Sakarynsky's Last Meal.
20世纪30年代的俄罗斯艺术电影
A Russian art film from the 1930s.
俄罗斯?
Russian?
字幕
Subtitles!
我饿了
I'm hungry.
你没碰巧保存了Kevin的什么创作吧?
You didn't happen to save any of Kevin's produce, did you?
Daria?
我们要被老师看到了
We're about to be seen with a teacher.
嗨 O'Neill老师
Hi, Mr. O'Neill.
嗨 孩子们 我太受鼓舞了
Hi, girls! I'm just so invigorated!
好的电影院是永恒的
Great cinema is timeless.
放在今天就拍不出那电影了吗?
Couldn't that movie have been made today?
我猜 要是你能找到人去发掘演员的话
I guess, if you could find someone to exhume the actors.
我能送你俩回家么?
Can I give you two a lift home?
不 不用客气 我们喜欢走路
No, that's okay. We love to walk.
嗯 今晚对于散长步来说最完美不过了
Yeah, it's a perfect night for a nice long stroll.
你不坐到前面去么 Daria?
Don't you want to sit in the front, Daria?
我很想 可是
I'd love to, but,
你懂的 我怕会被气囊弄伤
you know, I'm afraid of an airbag injury.
噢天啊 太抱歉了 我到底在想什么呀?
Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry, what was I thinking?
你当然得坐到后座去
Of course you must sit in the back!
有时候我觉得电影比小说更像是我们生活的影射
Sometimes I think film is even more a mirror of our times than the novel.
你觉得这是不是因为它更逼真?
Do you think this is because of its greater verisimilitude?
Jane?
我在后面听不到你说话啦
I can't really hear you back here.
公路噪音太大
Road noise.
另外 我不知道逼真是啥意思
Plus, I don't know what verisimilitude means.
你呢 Daria?
What about you, Daria?
面对现实吧
Let's face it.
多数人宁愿看电影都不愿意看书
Most people would rather watch a movie than read a book.
看电影更省事更简单 而且你压根不用担心嘴唇要运动
It's fast, it's easy, and you don't have to worry about your lips moving.
这是一项极好的课堂作业 Daria
That is a fabulous class assignment, Daria!
谢谢你的提议
Thank you for the suggestion!
我提什么议啦?
Um, did I make a suggestion?
要是提了的话 我恳请撤回
Because if so, I'd like to withdraw it.
所以咧 作为现实文学的练习
So, as an exercise in living literature,
你们都要自己制作电影
you'll all be making your own movies.
我们得谢谢Daria给出如此振奋的提议
We have Daria to thank for that exciting suggestion.
又是那个词
There's that word again.
好了 在我们分电影小组前
Now, before we split into movie making teams,
谁想当导演?
who would like to direct?
记住 这是个非常宝贵 精密 和非常非常贵的仪器
Remember, this is a precious, precise, and very, very costly instrument.
这可不是会随随便便借给青少年的东西
It's not the sort of thing one ordinarily lends a teenager.
我们会小心的
We'll be careful.
我和你解释过三种对焦模式啦
I explained to you about the three focus modes
还有归档覆盖以及自动睡眠功能
and the depth of field override and the auto-sleep feature.
我自己都快自动睡眠了
I'm about to go into auto-sleep myself.
好啦 Daria 就是... 尽量不要用它就好
Okay, Daria. Just... try not to use it too much.
好了 树像头
There. Tree-Cam.
你就这样把它开机扔在这?
You're just going to leave it running?
就扔个一两天
Only a day or two.
它会用树的客观视角来捕捉每一位路过的行人
It'll catch everyone passing by through the tree's totally objective point of view.
引人入胜
Riveting.
安迪·沃霍尔 波普艺术的倡导者和领袖
此处指其电影《沉睡》(Sleep 1963)
Andy Warhol拍了一个家伙睡8小时觉的片子
Andy Warhol filmed eight hours of a guy sleeping
而大家都觉得那很棒
and people thought it was brilliant.
接触到12步疗法后那些人就改变了想法
Those people changed their minds after they got into twelve step programs.
等等...
Wait...
我看到了树叶的摩擦
I think I just saw some leaves rustle.
那是我们的高潮
There's our climax.
也许我们需要一个剧本
Maybe we need a script.
然后你打开窗 说
And then you open the window and say,
"生活是无意义地堕入虚空
"Life is a meaningless descent into the void."
然后你跳下去 在坠落中尖叫
Then you jump, and on the way down you scream,
这下我可明白了 我什么都明白了"
"Now I understand, I understand everything."
你能去掉窗户的那段 给我点有意思的台词么?
Can you get rid of the window part and give me something funny to say?
再来只贵宾犬
And a poodle.
我真的超级想演我牵着贵宾犬散步耶
I'd really like to be in a scene where I'm walking a poodle.
真大牌
Actors.
"没有出路吗?"
"Is there no way out?"
此路不通 朋友
"No exit, my friend.
只剩我们被关在这房间里 千秋万世"
It's just us, stuck in this room together, forever and ever."
BY萨特 存在主义者
"救命 他人即地狱"
"Help! Hell is other people."
转念想想 自我即地狱
On second thought, hell is myself.
不对 宝贝 你得像有好几年没见到我一样跑向我
No, babe, you gotta run to me like you haven't seen me in years.
我之前在中国 记住了吗?
I've been in China, remember?
我只是在做慢动作 就像Jodie说的
I was trying to do it in slow motion, like Jodie said.
慢动作镜头是后期加的 你这傻X
You add the slow motion part after, you idiot.
是吗?
Don't you?
谁在乎啊 这真恶心
Who cares. This sucks.
我想拍超市罢工的电影
I really want to do a film about the supermarket strike.
可我都买了这套礼服 我穿这个可演不了收银员
But I already paid for this gown. I can't play a checkout girl in this.
是纪录片
It's a documentary.
你不需要礼服
You don't need the gown.
噢不 我才不要拍裸露片
Oh, no! I won't do a nude scene!
除非你说是角色特性的需要
Unless you think it's crucial to my character.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
我能借你的衣服出席今晚的时尚俱乐部派对么?
Can I borrow something to wear to the Fashion Club party tonight?
快检查她脑子是不是撞傻了
Check her head for bumps.
拜托啦 Daria?
Please, Daria?
是潮流禁穿晚会
It's the Fashion Don'ts Costume Gala.
你懂的 一个潮流禁穿晚会可以是一种... 电影素材
You know, a Fashion Don'ts Costume Party could be kind of... cinematic.
好的 告诉你怎么着 Quinn
Yeah. I'll tell you what,Quinn.
我会让你借我的衣服
I'll lend you an outfit,
但你今晚得让我拍摄你和你的朋友
but you have to let me videotape you and your friends tonight.
什么玩意 照相机么?
What, like, with a camera?
对 要拍电影 课堂作业
Yes. For a movie, for class.
我怎么会会拒绝你呢?
Why would I say no to that?
她有奇异的吸引力
She's strangely mesmerizing.
肤浅... 自恋... 自以为是...
Superficial... narcissistic... self-absorbed...
她有明星气质 搞定
she's got star quality, all right.
我喜欢你的禁穿打扮 Sandi
I love your don'ts, Sandi.
可瞧瞧你 Quinn
But look at you, Quinn:
方领上衣 下装太长 还配错鞋子
boxy top with too long bottom and the wrong shoes.
你到底在哪搞来这套装扮?
Where did you ever come up with that?
Quinn 你真是天才
Quinn, you're a genius.
我嘛 我就像艺术家 这就是姐表达自我的方式
I'm, like, an artist, and this is how I express myself!
噢 颜色真丑
Oh! Bad color!
她比录像带上还吓人
She's even scarier on tape.
这派对只是冰山一角
This party is just the tip of the iceberg.
我们发掘到了主题
We've found our subject.
你是说...
You mean...
Quinn Morgendorffer的一天
A day in the life of Quinn Morgendorffer.
你确定你想拍恐怖片?
Are you sure you want to do a horror movie?
所以他们要一整天都跟着我
So they're going to follow me around for a whole day.
或者一分钟 取决于我们能忍受多久
Or a minute, depending on how much we can stand.
能早早回家并有机会做晚饭真是好极了
It's so nice to get home early and have a chance to make dinner.
Quinn 你确定你要这么做?
Quinn, are you sure you want to do this?
你的隐私怎么办?
What about your privacy?
我们家的人什么时候变得这么害怕隐私外泄啦?
When did this family turn into such a bunch of privacy freaks?
哥的录像来喽
My video transfers!
真是迫不及待要重回童年啦
I can't wait to relive my childhood!
要吃完饭来看带子么?
Shall we watch after dinner?
我想我得在播映前写点小故事
I thought I'd write a little narration before the big screening.
我想抓住这个时期的本质
I want to capture the whole essence of the period.
我不记得你对这些日子有讨喜的记忆
I don't remember you having such fond memories of those days.
我全都想起来了
It's all coming back to me!
它真让人怀念童年
It really makes you feel nostalgic for your childhood.
这是你的黄金时刻
This is your golden time!
享受青春 女孩们
Enjoy your youth, girls.
我不吃甜点了 我不想明天看起来胖胖的
I think I'll pass on dessert. I don't want to look puffy tomorrow.
我猜我就自个儿去看会电视吧
I guess I'll go watch TV by myself for awhile.
当这些芭蕾舞者能在酒吧混得开 她们就能在酒吧混得开
When these ballerinas work out at the bar, they work out at the bar!
呕心小世界即将为您播映《喝醉的芭蕾舞裙》
Tanked in a tutu when Sick, Sad World returns.
进来
Come in.
Daria 我在想你能不能告诉我你对Quinn这部电影的想法?
Daria, I wonder if you'd tell me what you have in mind for this movie of Quinn.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
只是英语课要求的一项蹩脚作业而已
It's just a lame assignment for English class.
我说 干嘛要拍Quinn
I mean, why Quinn?
她有活力又上镜
Well, she's lively, she's photogenic.
你猜嘛? 她很活泼
You know what? She's bubbly.
Daria...
我们得一天都对Quinn进行跟踪拍摄
We're going to follow around Quinn for a day
并向世人展示有魅力又受欢迎是怎么一回事
and show the world what it's like to be attractive and popular.
我本人对那就很好奇
I'm kind of curious about that myself.
只是有时候
It's just that sometimes
你按很严格的标准去评价别人的行为
you judge people's behavior by a pretty rigid set of standards.
不是每个人都能按那一套生活
Not everyone can live up to them.
那就是这个世界的错误之处
That's what's wrong with the world.
甚至你自己也不是时刻遵守着那套
Not even you live up to them all the time.
我猜我能对她放宽点
I guess I could go easy on her.
谢谢 亲爱的
Thanks, sweetie.
不过不要惊讶哟
But don't hold your breath.
准备好了?
Ready?
放手大干吧
Rarin'.
记住 我们在揭露一个虚伪 以自我为中心的自大狂
Remember, we're exposing a hollow, self-centered egomaniac.
相信我 我们不需要太费劲
Trust me. We won't have to work very hard.
我们就说早晨不是她的黄金时刻好啦
Let's just say mornings are not her best time.
早上好呀 美丽的世界
Good morning, beautiful world.
你不是要拍我吗?
Don't you want to shoot me?
是啊 我是要拍你
Yes. I want to shoot you.
对了 话说我哪边脸比较好看?
By the way, which is my best side?
我知道两边都很美
I know they're both good.
你都已经化好妆了
You're already wearing makeup.
我没有
I am not!
我只是碰巧天生丽质 素颜就美
I just happen to be the kind of person who doesn't really need makeup.
那你化妆是因为...
So you're putting it on because...
不是每个人都像我一样幸运
Not everyone is as lucky as I am.
我想成为所有人的榜样
I want to be a role model for all people.
甚至是那些急需化妆的人
Even the ones who need makeup really badly.
我想我得坐下来 我有点晕了
I think I need to sit down. I'm getting dizzy.
人们 团结一致 永不分离
The people, united, will never be divided!
我不懂
I don't get it!
他们都站在那干嘛?
Why are they all standing there?
他们有管理纠纷 所以罢工了
They're having a dispute with management, so they refuse to work.
得有人告诉他们 他们占用人行道了
Someone should tell them they're taking up the sidewalk.
告诉我您为什么罢工 您希望这能达到什么目的
Tell me why you're on strike and what you hope to accomplish.
再简单不过了
It's simple enough:
有劳有得
an honest day's pay for an honest day's work,
停止剥削我们的利益
and stop chiseling away at our benefits!
我有东西想要 宝贝
I'm getting a craving, babe.
巧克力小蛋糕吗?
Ho-Hos?
对呀
Yeah!
没问题 宝贝
No problem, babe!
嘿 打扰啦
Hey! Escuse me...
力量瑜伽是一项很好的运动
Power yoga is a really good thing to do
因为内在美和外在美同样重要
because inner beauty is just as important as outer beauty.
就像 你能光有CD没有CD播放器么?
Like, can you have a CD without a CD player?
我可不这么认为
I don't think so!
那是纯真的年代
It was a time of innocence,
那个年代你不用锁门 一颗糖才卖五美分
when you left your doors unlocked and candy bars cost a nickel.
虽然两件事没关系 我...
Not that those two facts are related, I'm...
该死 让我从这开始
aww, dammit! Lemme start over here.
那是一段无忧无虑的时光
It was a carefree time
小男孩能在阳光照耀的大街上学骑单车
when a young boy could learn to ride a bike on sun-dappled streets.
嘿 嘿 为什么没有人帮帮那可怜的小孩?
Hey! Hey! Why doesn't anybody help that poor kid?
他擦伤了膝盖 噢我懂了
He skinned his knee! Oh, I get it.
"坐回单车上去 Jake 男子汉才不哭鼻子
"Get back on the bike Jake. Big boys don't cry.
女孩子才哭鼻子 Jakey"
Crying is for girls, Jakey."
摇摇晃晃 歪歪倒倒
Shake, shake, quiver and quake!
我现在可都想起来了
It's all coming back to me now!
不管我们去哪 你表姐和她小伙伴是不是得一直跟着?
Are your cousin and her friend going to follow us everywhere we go?
不是和你说了嘛 无视他们就好
I told you, just ignore them.
你总是这么说 可他们不是总是都拿着相机喽
You always say that about them, but they don't usually have a camera.
那是我参与的一项小研究 噢 强迫参与
It's a little project that I got, um, forced into.
对了 你觉得我哪边脸更美?
By the way, which do you think is my best side?
都很美
They're both good.
人家造啦 不过这边脸的酒窝更可爱耶
I know, but this side has my better dimples.
我不知道我还能忍多久
I don't know how much more of this I can take.
亲?
Um, guy?
你能去看看他们有没有不放芝士的披萨么?
Would you find out if they have those cheeseless pizzas?
- 好的 - 噢 他是 Zachary
- Sure! - And, uh, it's Zachary.
你干嘛邀请他一块来呀?
Why did you invite that guy?
我以为你这周是和Larry交往
I thought you were going steady with Larry this week.
Larry的车废了 Zachary能开他老妈的车
Larry totaled his car. Zachary's got his mom's car.
你可真聪明 Quinn 你总是能未雨绸缪
You're so smart, Quinn. You always think ahead.
听到了么 听到了么 亲们?
Did you hear that? Did you hear that, guys?
亲们?
Guys!
噢 看那可爱的小男孩
Oh, look at that cute little boy.
他长成了一个如此英俊的男子
And he grew up into such a handsome man.
亲爱的 你要开点灯吗?
Honey? Wouldn't you like a little more light in here?
好吧 Jake 我去厨房赶我的文书工作
Okay, Jake, I'm just going to catch up on some paperwork in the kitchen.
谢谢你送我们来 Aaron
Thanks for driving us here, Aaron.
我是Zachary.
It's Zachary.
我就是这么说
That's what I said.
可是购物是女孩子的事儿
But shopping is kind of a girl thing.
也许你能待会再来找我们
Maybe you could meet us after or something.
那我这期间要做什么?
But what will I do in the meantime?
不造耶 你有什么要买的吗?
I don't know. Do you have any shopping to do?
也许你想给什么特别的人买份礼物?
Maybe there's someone special you want to get a present for.
好吧 你就很特别 Quinn
Um, well, you're kind of special, Quinn.
噢 Zachary 你不用给人家买礼物了啦
Oh, Zachary, you don't have to get me a present.
要是你去Junior 5店找Theresa 说你是给Quinn买的
If you ask for Theresa in Junior 5 and tell her it's for Quinn,
她就会帮你搞定
she'll help you out.
你拍到没? 我希望你拍到了
Did you get that? I hope you got that.
你造"毛孔收敛"倒过来拼是"雷利法吸虫"吗?
Did you know that "pore refiner" spelt backwards is "renifer erop"?
把那给我
Give me that!
噢 看呀 收缩水
Oh, look! Pore refiner.
我真高兴我用不着那个
I'm glad I don't need that.
你有没有意识到为毛受欢迎的人的毛孔都很小?
Have you ever noticed how popular people always have the tiniest pores?
这又是为毛呢?
I wonder why that is?
你的毛孔都很可爱 Quinn
Your pores are very cute, Quinn.
可你看不到它们呀 对吧?
But you can't seem them, can you?
噢天啊 他们在... 他们在对焦
Oh, my God, they've been... they've been zooming!
你最好不要拉近 别再对焦了 我说真的
You better not zoom that thing. Stop zooming, I mean it.
要是在镜头上能看到我的任何一个毛孔 我发誓 我要宰了你
If you can see any of my pores on camera, I swear, I'll kill you.
别拍了 我才没有毛孔
Stop the tape! I do not have pores!
我的毛孔都很可爱 我的毛孔超小的
My pores are cute! My pores are tiny!
你被炒啦
You're fired!
不管你说什么都会被用来对付你
Anything you say can and will be used against you.
我们拍好啦
We've got our Quinn.
杀青喽
That's a wrap.
但是包臀裙绝对是时尚禁止
But a wrap is a definite don't.
我的天哟 这话真的是从我嘴里蹦出来的?
Oh, my God. Did I really just say that?
我有最可爱最细致的毛孔啦 对吧?
I have the cutest little pores, don't I?
当然啦 每一个都像是小酒窝
You really do. Each one is like a tiny dimple.
我希望我也能有你的毛孔 Daria
I wish I had pores like yours, Daria
"像你的毛孔"
"Pores Like Yours."
那对于毛孔调理磨砂膏来说真是好名字
That would be a great name for a pore conditioning exfoliant.
天呀 Daria 你是怎么做到的?
God, Daria, how do you do it?
我们在恭维你的完美毛孔
Here we are, complimenting you on your perfect pores,
而你却慈悲为怀地思考自己能怎么去改善他人的毛孔
and you're unselfishly thinking about how you can improve the pores of others.
pores与pours同音
我猜是下雨啦 就想到倾盆了
Duh! I guess when it rains, it "pores."
老爸 你在干嘛?
Dad? What are you doing up?
我是一个小宝宝 我需要照顾
I was a child. I needed attention.
我的膝盖受过轻伤
I had a boo-boo on my knee.
可是大体是痊愈了吧?
Uh, it's pretty much healed now, though. Right?
有人在乎么?
Did anyone care?
才没有人在乎呢
No one cared.
这就是我从未有过的 Daria
This is what I never had, Daria.
我们现在是这样做: 简单的亲子联系
What we're doing now: simple parent/child bonding.
我和你妈费了多大劲才让我们这样亲近
The kind of closeness your mother and I have worked so hard to give you.
天 真搞笑
Gee, that's funny.
我都能发誓我是从梦中醒来
I could've sworn I woke up from the dream.
你可不能给这样的时刻定价 Daria
You just can't put a price on a moment like this, Daria,
而且一旦这些日子远去 它们就是远去了
and once these years are gone, they're gone.
爸 都四点了
Dad, it's 4:00 A.M.
我刚才最可怕的噩梦醒来: 模仿我妹
I just woke up from my worst nightmare: resembling my sister.
你则在重温40年前的父母的疏忽照顾
You're reliving an instance of parental neglect from forty years ago.
你把这叫做亲子联系?
You call this parent/child bonding?
对我来说是
Works for me.
再看一遍吧
Let's watch again.
谢谢你来这碰头
Thanks for meeting me here.
看起来你昨晚过得不咋地啊
Looks like you had a rough night.
答应我如果我开始言行举止或者思考都和Quinn一样
Just promise me that if I start acting, talking, or thinking like Quinn,
你要做正确的事
you'll do the right thing.
要是药物治疗没效果 我会授权电击
If you don't respond to drug therapy, I'll authorize electric shock.
噢对了 你的小毛孔儿今天很萌噢
Oh, and by the way, your teensy-weensy pores look really cute today.
可我哪边脸比较美?
But which is my best side, hmm?
我造都很美啦
I know they're both good.
嘿 Daria
Hey, Daria.
我是不是忘了说是谁送我来的?
Did I forget to mention who drove me here?
要是在镜头上能看到我的任何一个毛孔 我发誓 我要宰了你
If you can see any of my pores on camera, I swear, I'll kill you.
别拍啦
Stop the tape!
这太简单了
This is too easy.
易如反掌
Shooting ducks in a barrel.
电影拍得咋样了?
How's that film project coming?
好极了
Pretty good.
自从你妹妹在她独舞汇演上摔倒 我都没见过你那么开心
I haven't seen you so amused since your sister fell at her dance recital.
是我摔倒了
That was me.
我知道是你们其中一个嘲笑另外一个啦
I knew it was one of you girls laughing at one of you girls.
能偷看一眼么?
Can I sneak a peek?
我们还在编辑
We're still editing.
Quinn很有银幕表现力
Quinn's got a real screen presence.
对了 我哪边脸比较美?
By the way, which is my best side?
我造两边都很美啦
I know they're both good.
要是你能在镜头上看到我的任何一个毛孔 我发誓 我要宰了你
If you can see any of my pores on camera, I swear, I'll kill you.
别拍啦 我才没有毛孔
Stop the tape! I do not have pores!
我的毛孔很可爱 我的毛孔超小的
My pores are cute! My pores are tiny!
你被炒啦
You're fired!
天啊 这有点残酷
Oh, my. This is a little cruel.
你确定你没把她说的话断章取义?
Are you sure you haven't taken her out of context?
她自创的语句
She creates her own context.
你造吗 Daria
You know, Daria,
我不会让Quinn拍一部显得她姐姐很滑稽的电影
I wouldn't let Quinn make a movie that made her sister look ridiculous.
她怎么会嘛?
How could she?
她压根不承认她已经拍了
She doesn't admit to having one.
告诉你怎么着 Daria 你爱咋咋地
I'll tell you what, Daria: you do what you think is right.
我不喜欢那话
I don't like the sound of that.
别担心 她显然高估了我的感受
Don't worry. She's clearly overestimated my conscious...
还假设我有感受
by assuming I have one at all.
对了 我哪边脸比较美?
By the way, which is my best side?
那是我的电影吗? 我能看吗?
Is that my movie? Can I see?
抱歉 可那会扰乱创意工程
Sorry, but that would interfere with the creative process.
瞧 我们就像演员 这就是我们怎么表达自我
See, we're like artists, and this is how we express ourselves.
你懂的
You understand.
我迫不及待要看啦
I can't wait to see it.
我只希望自己说的话不会很蠢
I just hope I don't sound stupid or anything.
人家本来就不会
Not that I would.
打消念头
Perish the thought.
我只是 我造有时候有部分人
I just, I know that sometimes certain types of people,
嫉妒心很强的人 会认为 她以为她谁呀?
jealous people, might think, who does she think she is?
因为我有时候就会这样想
Because I sometimes think that.
可我不允许自己这样想太久
But I can't let myself go on too long thinking that.
或是别的
Or anything else.
我是说 有时候我和Sandi Stacy还有Tiffany一起走下大厅
I mean, sometimes I'm walking down the hall with Sandi, Stacy, and Tiffany,
我突然就脱离了自我 旁观着 就好像
and suddenly I'm outside of myself, watching, and it's, like,
"这些女的是谁?
"Who are these girls?
她们除了男人 衣服 车子 就没别的可聊了么?"
Can't they talk about anything but guys, and clothes, and cars?"
可然后呢 我们还能聊什么嘛?
But then, what would we talk about?
你得擅长做某件事
You have to be good at something.
你读写什么的都很厉害
You're good at your reading and writing and stuff,
而你画画也很强
and you're good at your little paintings.
可这些微不足道吧?
They are miniscule, aren't they?
我发觉 有魅力又受欢迎 就是我擅长的事
I figure, being attractive and popular, that's what I'm good at.
也许这不是那么重要了啦 不过你懂嘛 这就是我擅长的
Maybe it's not that important, but, you know, it's what I can do.
作孽
Aw, hell.
嗯
Yeah.
Jodie 你是从哪学到欺骗象征手法的?
Jodie, where did you learn to juggle symbolism like that?
我用了情节串联图板 我猜那有帮助吧
Um, I worked with storyboards. I think that helped.
接下来 Daria和Jane的作品
And now, a work by Daria and Jane.
我想成为所有人的榜样
I want to be a role model for all people,
甚至是那些急需化妆的人
even the ones that need makeup really badly.
对了 我哪边脸比较美?
By the way, which is my best side?
就好像 你能光有CD没有CD播放器么?
Like, can you have a CD without a CD player?
我可不这么认为
I don't think so.
对了 我哪边脸比较美?
By the way, which is my best side?
别弄得好像你化了浓妆
Don't look like you have on too much makeup.
化裸妆让你看起来像没怎么化
Wear enough to make it look like you don't have much on.
对了 我哪边脸比较美?
By the way, which is my best side?
晚安
Goodnight.
谢谢你和我分享我的一天
Thanks for sharing my day with me.
记住 时尚代表着趣味
And remember, fashion is fun and everything,
但我们得身体力行地为雨林做点事
but we should really do something about the rainforest and stuff.
那什么玩意?
What was that?
我和她说我再给她个机会
I told her I'd give her the opportunity
去展示自己的内心并不肤浅
to show there was more to her than the surface Quinn.
结果发现她还是没变
Turns out there isn't.
那毛孔那段到底去哪了? 我们最终完工的呢?
And what exactly happened to the pore stuff? Our big finish?
你造那个我没有的感受吧 我有了
You know the conscious I don't have? It got to me.
肤浅的深度 的确很刺激
The Depths of Shallowness. Provocative indeed.
现在 如果我们...
Now, what if we...
伙计们 你俩的电影确实屌炸天
Your movie really kicked butt, guys.
那是
Oh, sure.
我说真的 它真有捕捉到一种绝望
I mean it! It really captured a kind of despair.
你妹让我好悲伤
Your sister makes me so sad.
我也是
You and me both.
你是那个电影女孩 我爱你
You're the girl from the movie! I love you.
我哪边脸比较美? 你能告诉我吗?
Which is my best side? Can you tell me?
现在我才真是悲伤
Now I'm really sad.
天哟 我以为我是唯一一个为毛孔耻辱的人
God, I thought I was the only one ashamed of my pores.
我们都耻辱毛孔 可你不能耻辱自己的耻辱
We're all ashamed of our pores, but you mustn't be ashamed of your shame.
瞧 你好心做坏事啦
So, you did the compassionate thing, and look where it got you.
她比以前更受欢迎了
She's more popular than ever.
我们着手做揭露 结果成情书
We set out to make an exposé, it ends up a love letter.
瞧见没 我们就像艺术家 这就是我们如何表达自我
See, we're like artists, and this is how we screw ourselves.
至于你 你也能拥有富有弹性的秀发
And you, too, can have bouncy hair
如果你有时间把它从里往外卷
if you just take the time to bounce from the inside as well.
来吧 大家 和我一起弹起来
Come on, everyone! Bounce with me!
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组